JUAN GONZÁLEZ IGLESIAS

A Coruña, Spain https://www.juanchan.es 638917341 Linkedin Github juan.gonzalez1@udc.es

About me

Graduated in Computer Engineering, with dual specialization in Information Technologies and Computer Engineering, holding two Cybersecurity master's degrees, one from the University of A Coruña (MUNICS) and another from Deloitte. With two years of experience, currently employed at the Automotive Technology Center of Galicia as a Cybersecurity Engineer, I consider myself deeply passionate about this field and the IoT world, focusing on areas such as pentesting, vulnerability analysis and exploitation, hardening, forensics, as well as requirements and risk analysis. And above all, an ardent technology and security enthusiast with a positive attitude and an eagerness to continue learning and pursue a successful career.

Experience

Security Engineer, Ctag (Centro de la automoción de Galicia)

May 2023 - Now

- Conducted Vulnerability Analysis and Penetration Testing against multiple car prototipes and car systems, identifying and addressing security flaws.
- Developing scripts and executing attacks to assess the security of cars.
- Effectively conducted Security Management audits and wrote reports on the results obtained.
- Wireless hacking such as ARP Spoofing, DNS poisoning, WiFi Cracking, RF attacks and BTLe attacks.
- Conducted requirement analysis and TARA, applying ISO 21434 and UNECE R155.

Security Engineer, Enxenio

Sep 2022 - May 2023

- Penetration testing and security analysis for web applications.
- Creation, development, and maintenance of a SOC based on Wazuh.
- Implementation of continuous integration tools SAST and DAST.
- Vulnerability Management and audit report generation.

Education

MS in Cybersecurity, Universidade da Coruña (Munics)

Sep 2021 - Feb 2023

• Relevant Coursework: Crypto, Forensics, MobileSec, Malware Analysis, InfoSec, and Law.

MS in Cybersecurity, Deloitte x IMF

Sep 2022 - Feb 2023

• Relevant Coursework: SIEM technology, Ethical Hacking, Reverse Engineering and Secure Development.

Engineering in Computer Science, Universidadde da Coruña

Sep 2016 - Jun 2021

- Mention in Information Technologies
- Mention in Computer Engineering

Programming Lenguages and Technologies

- Proficient: Python, Git, AWS, Java, C, UNIX systems, HIDS/NIDS, Docker, SO Hardenind and SAST/DAST
- Intermediate: Web techonologies, CAN, Mobile, Databases (SQL), BTLe, Radio Frequency and Networks

Publications, Technical Experience and Honors

Publications

• Mobile application and monitoring of a dummy for training in emergency medical situations.

Enhancing a rescue dummy with monitoring technology and a mobile app to visualize vital data, facilitating efficient learning and aiding rescuers with critical information during emergency operations. MH and awarded for the best applied Bachelor's Thesis at the Faculty of Computer Science of A Coruña.

Sample of Personal Projects

More projects available on my website

• Researched [I]loT and Camera Hacking, studied UAV GPS security and created a Twitter bot and a Shopping bot using Python.

Languages

Spanish and Galician (Bilingual Proficient), English (Professional Proficient) and Portuguese (Familiar).